### SENIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

# Vinícius Siqueira

♀ im vinisiqueira00 ♦ +55 22 99274-3135 ☑ vinicius.siqueira642@gmail.com

I am a developer with over 7 years of experience, with almost 4 and a half years focused on front-end web development using ReactJS. Proficient in UI Design and back-end, I have gained experience at major players, using current technologies such as Next.js, NestJS, and Tailwind.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TROTESSIONAL EXPERIE	INCL		
Front-end Developer	Cadastra (M3 Ecommerce)	🛱 Aug, 2020 - Present	(~4 years and 4 months)
<ul> <li>Implemented e-commerce so</li> <li>Gained proficiency in various and marketplace.</li> <li>Worked on national (Brazil) a team members and improving</li> <li>Participated in squads dedica with the client's internal team</li> <li>Developed significant solutio capacity (VTEX/iFood) and an</li> </ul>	Figma for both internal and client lutions using VTEX, focusing on u VTEX functionalities, including or and LATAM (Argentina, Chile, Color g Spanish communication skills. Ited to major national retail players a using agile methodology (Scrum) ans, such as an internal management integration solution between VT and delivered a notable project: a scests) daily at a specific time.	ser experience. rderform, session, masterda mbia) projects, collaborating s like Carrefour Brasil and R . nt system for controlling dis EX and GShop.	with <b>Spanish-speaking</b> i <b>Happy</b> , integrating  stributed <b>delivery</b>
		our (Carriera) Culta Malana	ole CChair Ourse
Load Balancing Clean code Sc	S Figma ReactJS NodeJS Ja rum Communication Independe		ck GShop Queues
Load Balancing Clean Code Sc	rum Communication independe	nce	
Full-stack Developer	friweb - Agência Digital	🛱 Jan, 2019 - Jun, 2020	(~1 year and 5 months)
<ul> <li>Achieved a level of independent and indirectly involved in.</li> <li>Developed payment gateway</li> </ul>	pper on legacy PHP projects. for the implementation and evoluence, commitment, and responsib r integration for an e-commerce place platform built entirely in PHP a	ility to make decisions on patform, a mock exam platfo	
PHP HTML CSS JS JQu	ery Communication Leadership	Responsibility Independe	nce
Full-stack Developer	CEFET/RJ - Fábrica de Soft	ware 📛 Jan, 2018 -	Dec, 2018 (~11 months)
<ul><li>Worked in design, creating lo</li><li>Actively participated in the do</li></ul>	I designers to serve the non-profit gos and visual identities. evelopment of a registration syste project implementation process, f	em for a local event.	ry.
PHP HTML CSS JS Fign	Agile Methodology Communi	cation Leadership	

## ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

2 wertetor o tit Ingormation o joverno			
🛱 Jun, 2023	CEFET/RJ - UnED Nova Friburgo		

**Bachelor's in Information Systems** 

Technical Degree in Information Technology